[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0034_thealliance",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0034_d_00_container_thealliance",
        "NpcDestinationId": "NPC_9902_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_33",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0034_thealliance_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0034_thealliance_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0034_thealliance_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0034_thealliance_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0034_thealliance_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0034_thealliance_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0034_thealliance_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0035_herewestand",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0035_d_00_container_herewestand",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_35",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_34 || 99C_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0035_herewestand_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0035_herewestand_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0035_herewestand_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0035_herewestand_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0035_herewestand_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0035_herewestand_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0035_herewestand_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_35",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_v2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest_v2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_35",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_v2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_solo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest_solo",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36_b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_36_b_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_solo_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_solo_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_solo_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9919_0037_planb",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9919_0037_d_00_container_planb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905c_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_37",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9919_0037_planb_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9919_0037_planb_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9919_0037_planb_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9919_0037_planb_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9919_0037_planb_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9919_0037_planb_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0037_planb_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0038_itstrueface",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 42,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0038_d_00_container_itstrueface",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903c_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_38",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_37",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0038_itstrueface_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0039_aherosduty",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 43,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0039_d_00_container_aherosduty",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903c_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_39",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_38",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0039_aherosduty_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0040_emilesrequest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 44,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0040_d_00_container_emilesrequest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903d_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_40",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_39",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0040_emilesrequest_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0041_somethinglefttosave",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0041_d_00_container_somethinglefttosave",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903d_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_41",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_40",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0042_shecameback",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 46,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0042_d_00_container_shecameback",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905d_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_42",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_41",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0042_shecameback_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0042_shecameback_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0042_shecameback_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0042_shecameback_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0042_shecameback_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0042_shecameback_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0042_shecameback_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0043_foragoodcause",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 47,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0043_d_00_container_foragoodcause",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9909_MSQ_AEVillager3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_43",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_42",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0043_foragoodcause_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9909_0044_mothertongue",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 48,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9909_0044_d_00_container_mothertongue",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905d_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_44",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_43",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9909_0044_mothertongue_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0045_thebox",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0045_d_00_container_thebox",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_45",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_44",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0045_thebox_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0045_thebox_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0045_thebox_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0045_thebox_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0045_thebox_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0045_thebox_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0045_thebox_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0046_stemthetide",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0046_d_00_container_stemthetide",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_46",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_45",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0046_stemthetide_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0047_greatminds",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 51,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0047_d_00_container_greatminds",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904d_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_47",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_46",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0047_greatminds_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0047_greatminds_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0047_greatminds_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0047_greatminds_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0047_greatminds_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0047_greatminds_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0047_greatminds_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0048_d_00_container_enemyofmyenemy",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_48",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_47",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0049_recipeforfailure",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 53,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0049_d_00_container_recipeforfailure",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_49",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_48",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0049_recipeforfailure_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0050_thescenicroute",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9906_0050_d_00_container_thescenicroute",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_50",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_49",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0050_thescenicroute_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0051_ararespice",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9906_0051_d_00_container_ararespice",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_50b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_50",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0051_ararespice_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9906_0051_ararespice_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9906_0051_ararespice_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9906_0051_ararespice_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9906_0051_ararespice_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9906_0051_ararespice_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9906_0051_ararespice_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_51",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_50b",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0052_saboteur",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0052_d_00_container_saboteur",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_51",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0052_saboteur_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0052_saboteur_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0052_saboteur_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0052_saboteur_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0052_saboteur_v2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0052_d_00_container_saboteur_v2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_51",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0052_saboteur_v2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0052_saboteur_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0052_saboteur_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0052_saboteur_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0052_saboteur_solo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0052_d_00_container_saboteur_solo",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52_b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52_b_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0052_saboteur_solo_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0052_saboteur_solo_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0052_saboteur_solo_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52a",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9907_MSQ_AEVillager1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9908_MSQ_AEVillager2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52c",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task3",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_53",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0054_ASelflessNature",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0054_d_00_container_ASelflessNature",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_54",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52a \u0026\u0026 99_MSQ_52b \u0026\u0026 99_MSQ_52c \u0026\u0026 99_MSQ_53",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0054_ASelflessNature_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0055_shatteredmountain",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0055_d_00_container_shatteredmountain",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9910_MSQ_AEScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_55",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_54",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0055_shatteredmountain_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9910_0056_thetempestsheart",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0056_d_00_container_thetempestsheart",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_56",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_55",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0056_thetempestsheart_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0057_insoulinstone",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0057_d_00_container_insoulinstone",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_56",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0057_insoulinstone_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQFinale",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9910_0058_finallyexhale",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0058_d_00_container_finallyexhale",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905e_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0059_InMemoriam",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0059_d_00_container_InMemoriam",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9928_MSQ_YonasMemorial",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_59",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9926_0101_d_00_container_TenaciousRose",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9926_VK_AbigailRoseB",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0101",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 28,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9926_0103_d_00_container_LostScarecrow",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9930_VK_RomacBarboB",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0103",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9932_0104_d_00_container_RelicReclamation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9931_VK_Caoimhe",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0104",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": true
    }
]
